### Privacy Policy

The Bill Organizer Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures and covers all of the products and services contained on those websites. Our Policy explains what data we collect from you, how we collect it, and the use of the data collected from you.

Bill Organizer never sells your information to any third party for monetary purposes, advertising, or promotions. We guarantee the security of your data. The Bill Organizer Privacy Policy also discloses information about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.

### What Information Do We Collect?

We collect the information that helps us know our customers better and deliver more satisfactory services and user experiences. Customers share the information when they contact us using email, contact forms, or lead generation forms asking for our services.

We store that information for future use in developing your projects and analyzing your requirements. The information that we gather include:

### Personal Data

We may ask you to provide us with certain personal information that we can use to contact or identify you or your business. The information may include:

* Email address
* First name and last name
* Phone number
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
* Usage Data

We may also collect Personal Data from your Third-Party Social Media Service accounts (Google, Facebook, Twitter), such as your activities or your contact list associated with that account.

### Usage Data

Usage Data is the information that is collected automatically when using the Service. It may include information such as the Device’s IP address, browser type, browser version, your browsing histories like the service pages that you visit, the time and date of your visit, as well as the time spent and other data.

Suppose a user accesses the Service through a mobile device. In that case, we collect certain information automatically, including the type of mobile device, mobile device unique ID, the IP address of the mobile device, mobile operating system, mobile Internet browser, unique device identifiers, and other data.

### Cookies and Tracking Technologies

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the user activities on our service pages and website. The tracking technologies we use include beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and improve and analyze Our Services.

**Cookies or Browser Cookies.** A cookie is a small file placed on the device of users. Users can choose to refuse or disable certain Cookies. However, if users do not accept cookies, they may not use some parts of our Service.

**Web Beacons** We may use small electronic files known as web beacons in our Service and emails that permit Bill Organizer to collect the website and visitors statistics. For example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and recorded the popularity of a specific section, verifying system and server integrity.

We use both “Persistent” and “Session” Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device when you go offline, while Session Cookies get deleted the moment you close your web browser.

Certain features of our Service may use Flash Cookies that are local stored objects to collect and store information about your preferences or your activity on our Service. The Browser settings for Flash Cookies are different than settings used for Browser Cookies.

### How do we use your information?

We use the collected information to analyze user needs, develop better solutions, and provide the same services you’ve requested. We also use this data to provide you with the details about the services you’re currently using, customer support requests or offers on new services. In addition, we use it to gather user feedback and communicate policy updates.

The Users can decline certain kinds of information use either by not providing the information or by opting out later. We provide limited access to your personal information to our employees and vendors only for legitimate use.

We use your data for imparting more suitable and improved Service. By using the Service, You agree to collect your data and information per this Privacy Policy.

### We may use your Data for the following purposes:

* Develop and deliver services as well as monitor the usage of our Service.
* To manage your account as a registered user of our services. We provide you access to different functionalities of our Service as a registered user.
* To use the contract for the products, items, or services used or purchased by you.
* Contact you by email, telephone calls, SMS, or others such as push notifications in mobile apps regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products, or contracted services. For instance, app updates, special offers, and general information about other goods and services we offer.
* To attend and manage the requests sent by users to Bill Organizer.
* Bill Organizer may use your information for other purposes, such as for data analysis, understanding usage trends, to evaluate and improve our Service, products, services, marketing, and user experience.

### Who we share your data with

We disclose your personal information only with your consent. Bill Organizer processes and operates your Personal Data at the Company’s operating offices. We may share or transfer this information to other computers outside the state, province, or country. Bill Organizer ensures that your data is treated securely and per this Privacy Policy.

### How long do we retain your data?

We keep your personal information for as long as it is required for legitimate purposes. When we no longer need to process your information, we delete, anonymize, or isolate your information, whichever is appropriate.

The comments and their metadata are retained eternally. Retention of this information helps us automatically recognize and approve any follow-up comments instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

If any users register on our website, we store the personal information they provide in their user profiles. They can see, edit, or delete their personal information except for their username. The website administrator also has the right to edit this information.

### How long do we retain your data?

We disclose which categories of Personal Data we collect and the purposes for collecting and using the Personal Data. The users can request to disclose information about personal data usage. Users can refuse to share their private information.

Users can also request to delete the Personal Data, subject to certain exceptions. We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or to keep it for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We regularly review the Privacy Policy to ensure compliance with the latest data protection laws and practices for transparency in our services. We notify and inform our users about any updates made in the Privacy Policy and post the new Privacy Policy on the same page.

We notify users via email before the change becomes effective, explicitly mentioning the last updated date. Users can review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

© Bill organizer. All rights reserved.
